[{"answer": "The event was a Toys for Tot annual toy drive that Paul Walker and Roger put on every year.", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 21, "question": "Obviously, devastating things sort of happened not just for all his fans and his family but if everyone who was at this event that you were at a charity, then tell me what the event was and how he had seemed at event itself before this crash?", "qSentId": 20}, {"answer": "Well, when Roger and Paul drove by us, I was standing by several of the cars, a Ford GT and a Ferrari that belongs to a friend of mine and they said \"We'll be back in five minutes.\"", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 31, "question": "When he left, did you have any idea how of long they'll be going to be out in the car or they due (ph) to come back in it?", "qSentId": 30}, {"answer": "Well, I heard the car go by us and, you know, I heard them go through their gears and then drive and I said \"Hey, there goes the Porsche\" and \"Oh, looks great, everything's nice.\"", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 35, "question": "What did you see on here?", "qSentId": 34}, {"answer": "They're gone -- it seem like five minutes but it was longer.", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 56, "question": "How long have they been out when you saw them get past you seconds before the crash?", "qSentId": 55}, {"answer": "(inaudible) test driving the car.", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 66, "question": "And what kind of speed you think?", "qSentId": 65}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I never sound really go fast so it's kind of hard because when they pull out of the parking lot, they were going very slow.", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 68, "question": "What kind of speed?", "qSentId": 67}, {"answer": "That's correct.", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 75, "question": "So from everything that you've seen at the scene, none of those tire marks that we're looking at now could actually have come from the Porsche itself?", "qSentId": 74}, {"answer": "The tires are much wider on the Porsche than what's Honda or Toyota, these tire marks are six to eight inches wide, the minimum size tire on a Porsche is 12 to 18 inches wide or wider.", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 77, "question": "And that is because the tires are much wider on the Porsche, is that right?", "qSentId": 76}, {"answer": "Well, of course something tragically happened, so I'm not being by (ph) on the vehicle I can't speculate on exactly what it was or anything else and I'm not even going to try to guess because two of our friends had passed in this.", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 81, "question": "Remember the thing that you have seen and gleaned from the scene there, what would your best guess be about the likely cause of what happened here?", "qSentId": 80}, {"answer": "Well, from what I, you know, from what I know of Paul with his charitable company with Ro, the guy would take the shirt of his back to help you.", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 88, "question": "How would you describe Paul Walker for those who didn't know him?", "qSentId": 87}, {"answer": "Yes, I mean another sad part of the story is that Paul Walker was in the middle of probably the best part of his career.", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 105, "question": "Tell me about where he was Paul Walker with his movie current, in particular with the Fast and Furious franchise which I think was in the, it was seventh movie which is pretty much nearly finished, right?", "qSentId": 104}, {"answer": "Well that's the situation the Universal Studios is in this week, they're really trying to figure out exactly what to do.", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "How the movie studios deal with this kind of crisis when it happens?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "Well, you know, the thing is everybody who's ever worked with Paul Walker, the people that we spoken with have really said this is an outstanding guy, you know, he was nicest guy on set, those kinds of comments, you know.", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 130, "question": "I mean, are you picking up anything in Hollywood from anyone there about what may have gone on here?", "qSentId": 129}, {"answer": "It is, it is, it has a lot of twist and turns, I think Shonda Rhimes is done in amazing job at dramatizing it for television, it's great.", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 171, "question": "I mean, Kerry wasn't fairly shock, I mean, it's not -- but people really don't want chase, it's very addictive because instead of a pop drama, pop comedy, it's a really interesting way that they've made it, isn't it?", "qSentId": 170}, {"answer": "Yes, it is.", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 175, "question": "Is that lethal computer of sex and scandal, isn't it?", "qSentId": 174}, {"answer": "I think probably the most difficult one is that sort of combination that you mentioned that sex is politics, it's corruption for the media has all of those things that are just sexy and juicy so I think those are pretty ...", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 178, "question": "What is the most difficult crisis, generically, to manage in your experience?", "qSentId": 177}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, when you think about it, it's the President of the United States and of course all eyes are watching you and how you navigate through a crisis.", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 181, "question": "What was it -- was it like the way Scandal portrays the scandalous stuff involving the president, is that what is really like in real life?", "qSentId": 180}, {"answer": "I think social media has made my job so much more difficult.", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 189, "question": "And how do you deal with that particularly development now in the process of a scandal?", "qSentId": 188}, {"answer": "Well, I think if you are sitting in that position the network is going to weigh how the audience feels.", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 223, "question": "How do crisis manage Alec Baldwin with this kind of scenario?", "qSentId": 222}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 230, "question": "Is there any easier way to manage it?", "qSentId": 229}, {"answer": "MITH: I think that they have to look at each case and they're going to look at quite frankly where they're getting pushback from how people reacting to it.", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 242, "question": "Even thought Martin Bashir, one of their cable guys came out with a comment that many people believes or analogy about slavery and Sarah Palin and so on which many believe is much more offensive and yet he remained on air is there a hypocrisy there or double standard?", "qSentId": 241}, {"answer": "Well --", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 250, "question": "I want to know what you would do now is there anything that can be done to save ObamaCare?", "qSentId": 249}, {"answer": "And the problem seems to me is that he, you know, it's all very well said that we got a few things wrong.", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 270, "question": "I think the question is going to be how he moves past this?", "qSentId": 269}, {"answer": "I don't think it's too late.", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 293, "question": "Is it terminally damaged ObamaCare?", "qSentId": 292}, {"answer": "Two things.", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 316, "question": "What is the best way he can do it?", "qSentId": 315}, {"answer": "Well I think somebody needs to be held accountable ...", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 322, "question": "Doesn't Kathleen Sebelius have to be sacrificed for the greater good?", "qSentId": 321}, {"answer": "Yes, they do.", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 326, "question": "... people get fired, right?", "qSentId": 325}, {"answer": "I would probably tell him that some of his have to roll for it, absolutely.", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 337, "question": "Would you tell him to fire Kathleen Sebelius?", "qSentId": 336}, {"answer": "Someone.", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 339, "question": "Including hers?", "qSentId": 338}, {"answer": "Somewhat.", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 341, "question": "There's nobody more appropriate, right?", "qSentId": 340}, {"answer": "Yes, I think Hillary has an amazing track record.", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 347, "question": "... is any of that stuff going to stick when it comes to a Hillary run as most people expect her to do?", "qSentId": 346}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 353, "question": "Is his weight a genuine issue for the American people after a fifth athletic President who turned out to be not quite what people thought?", "qSentId": 352}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 366, "question": "You wouldn't have this conversation?", "qSentId": 365}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 382, "question": "... Barrack Obama turned out to be?", "qSentId": 381}, {"answer": "I wouldn't.", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 423, "question": "Would you take on a guy like him?", "qSentId": 422}, {"answer": "That's a hard one.", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 429, "question": "What's worst for a politician, drugs or sex as a scandal, or corruption?", "qSentId": 428}, {"answer": "I say drugs.", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 431, "question": "Drugs, sex, or corruption?", "qSentId": 430}, {"answer": "I think two things.", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 441, "question": "When you see, you know, much more liberal views on things like cannabis, whether it should be legalized, gay rights, and so on, should we still be pillaring and driving out of office, people who are in political life who have personal transgressions?", "qSentId": 440}, {"answer": "No, no.", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 453, "question": "And you can't go back like Anthony Weiner didn't turn the tap back on?", "qSentId": 452}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 457, "question": "Is it (inaudible) when you sit down with the politicians, some particularly politician who's been caught up in a sex scandal, is he embarrassing when you sit there and they have to unburden themselves to be sitting with Olivia Pope on the show?", "qSentId": 456}, {"answer": "Not shocked.", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 464, "question": "Are you ever so shocked you just can't carry on with the conversation?", "qSentId": 463}, {"answer": "Yeah, I think there are three things.", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 472, "question": "What is it that makes the difference in how you come through and end up potentially being very popular again?", "qSentId": 471}, {"answer": "No, no, no, not...", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 511, "question": "... is yours like that?", "qSentId": 510}, {"answer": "No, no, no, not sleeping with any President.", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 513, "question": "ORGAN: Anything you want to share with me about the previous Presidents?", "qSentId": 512}, {"answer": "Oh yeah.", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 521, "question": "And the show itself always is huge on Twitter and Facebook and so on, isn't it?", "qSentId": 520}, {"answer": "We love it, we love it.", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "She is absolutely fantastic isn't she?", "qSentId": 534}, {"answer": "Yeah, I mean you have to be, you have to be.", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 539, "question": "Is everything base it in your head a quick check list of boom, boom, boom, boom are you like that?", "qSentId": 538}, {"answer": "It is 24/7 a little bit of sleep and yeah, you have to be I guess.", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 544, "question": "Is that a reality?", "qSentId": 543}, {"answer": "About five hours a night, I'm good on five.", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 546, "question": "How much sleep you get?", "qSentId": 545}, {"answer": "It is, it is it's not that kind of job that if you want to have a nine to five.", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 548, "question": "It's just relentless isn't it?", "qSentId": 547}, {"answer": "I do, I do.", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 551, "question": "Do you watch the show?", "qSentId": 550}, {"answer": "I do, I do, I tell you one day it was very funny.", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 553, "question": "Because I know you helped produce it but did you watch it?", "qSentId": 552}, {"answer": "I did, I did.", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 578, "question": "Did you?", "qSentId": 577}, {"answer": "I would say, don't count the women that are natural wife, no, no, no.", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 596, "question": "If I had one of your clients sitting there, knowing that I would ask that, what would you tell them to say?", "qSentId": 595}, {"answer": "Yes I would, honesty is always the best policy.", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 598, "question": "Would you tell them to be honest with that answer?", "qSentId": 597}, {"answer": "Oh god that's a tough one.", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 604, "question": "What's been the greatest moment of your life?", "qSentId": 603}, {"answer": "Here lies Judy Smith.", "docId": "131202pmt", "aSentId": 611, "question": "What I wanted to do?", "qSentId": 610}]